[
	{
		"question": "吧",
		"pinyin": "ba",
		"optionA": "love; affection; be fond of",
		"optionB": "to let down",
		"optionC": "particle indicating polite suggestion; | onomatopoeia | bar (serving drinks, providing internet access, etc.)",
		"optionD": "if you please",
		"answer": "particle indicating polite suggestion; | onomatopoeia | bar (serving drinks, providing internet access, etc.)"
	},

	{
		"question": "白",
		"pinyin": "bái",
		"optionA": "white; snowy; pure; bright; empty (Kangxi radical 106)",
		"optionB": "excuse me",
		"optionC": "unworthy",
		"optionD": "eight (Kangxi radical 12)",
		"answer": "white; snowy; pure; bright; empty (Kangxi radical 106)"
	},

	{
		"question": "百",
		"pinyin": "bǎi",
		"optionA": "to read",
		"optionB": "hundred",
		"optionC": "(informal) father; Dad",
		"optionD": "Dan Brown",
		"answer": "hundred"
	},

	{
		"question": "帮助",
		"pinyin": "bāng zhù",
		"optionA": "to help; to assist; to aid",
		"optionB": "A Computer",
		"optionC": "A pair of shoes",
		"optionD": "cup; glass",
		"answer": "to help; to assist; to aid"
	},

	{
		"question": "报纸",
		"pinyin": "bào zhǐ",
		"optionA": "Beijing (capital of China)",
		"optionB": "Elephant",
		"optionC": "Goat",
		"optionD": "newspaper",
		"answer": "newspaper"
	},

	{
		"question": "比",
		"pinyin": "bǐ",
		"optionA": "doctor",
		"optionB": "compare; (indicates comparison) (Kangxi radical 81); to gesticulate as one talks",
		"optionC": "Sherlock Holmes",
		"optionD": "Samuel L. Jackson",
		"answer": "compare; (indicates comparison) (Kangxi radical 81); to gesticulate as one talks"
	},

	{
		"question": "别",
		"pinyin": "bié",
		"optionA": "don't do something; don't | depart; | other; difference; distinguish",
		"optionB": "Blue",
		"optionC": "no; not",
		"optionD": "to study",
		"answer": "don't do something; don't | depart; | other; difference; distinguish"
	},

	{
		"question": "宾馆",
		"pinyin": "bīn guǎn",
		"optionA": "you're welcome; don't be polite; impolite",
		"optionB": "guesthouse; hotel",
		"optionC": "legs",
		"optionD": "hands",
		"answer": "guesthouse; hotel"
	},

	{
		"question": "长",
		"pinyin": "cháng",
		"optionA": "play",
		"optionB": "10",
		"optionC": "long; length | grow; chief (Kangxi radical 168)",
		"optionD": "dish (type of food); vegetables",
		"answer": "long; length | grow; chief (Kangxi radical 168)"
	},

	{
		"question": "唱歌",
		"pinyin": "chàng gē",
		"optionA": "sing (a song)",
		"optionB": "Horse racing",
		"optionC": "Street Racing",
		"optionD": "Arm Wrestling",
		"answer": "sing (a song)"
	},

	{
		"question": "出",
		"pinyin": "chū",
		"optionA": "music",
		"optionB": "Sir Isaac Newton",
		"optionC": "eat",
		"optionD": "go out; occur",
		"answer": "go out; occur"
	},

	{
		"question": "穿",
		"pinyin": "chuān",
		"optionA": "taxi; cab",
		"optionB": "The Dictionary",
		"optionC": "to wear; put on; penetrate",
		"optionD": "The Chemistry text Book",
		"answer": "to wear; put on; penetrate"
	},

	{
		"question": "次",
		"pinyin": "cì",
		"optionA": "go to work",
		"optionB": "(mw for number of times of occurrence); nth; order",
		"optionC": "Abuja",
		"optionD": "Syndey",
		"answer": "(mw for number of times of occurrence); nth; order"
	},

	{
		"question": "从",
		"pinyin": "cóng",
		"optionA": "pen",
		"optionB": "to read",
		"optionC": "to interpret",
		"optionD": "from; obey; observe",
		"answer": "from; obey; observe"
	},

	{
		"question": "错",
		"pinyin": "cuò",
		"optionA": "mistake; error; blunder; miss an opportunity",
		"optionB": "Barack Obama",
		"optionC": "Wole Soyinka",
		"optionD": "Thomas Edison",
		"answer": "mistake; error; blunder; miss an opportunity"
	},

	{
		"question": "打篮球",
		"pinyin": "dǎ lán qiú",
		"optionA": "to learn",
		"optionB": "to decipher",
		"optionC": "play basketball",
		"optionD": "At that time",
		"answer": "play basketball"
	},

	{
		"question": "大家",
		"pinyin": "dà jiā",
		"optionA": "television; TV",
		"optionB": "movie; film",
		"optionC": "everyone",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "everyone"
	},

	{
		"question": "到",
		"pinyin": "dào",
		"optionA": "arrive (at a place); until (a time)",
		"optionB": "television; TV",
		"optionC": "computer",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "arrive (at a place); until (a time)"
	},

	{
		"question": "得",
		"pinyin": "de",
		"optionA": "tea",
		"optionB": "television; TV",
		"optionC": "computer",
		"optionD": "(complement particle)",
		"answer": "(complement particle)"
	},

	{
		"question": "等",
		"pinyin": "děng",
		"optionA": "to wait; rank; equal; etc.",
		"optionB": "television; TV",
		"optionC": "computer",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "to wait; rank; equal; etc."
	},

	{
		"question": "弟弟",
		"pinyin": "dì di",
		"optionA": "thing; objects; stuff; (-xī: east and west)",
		"optionB": "younger brother",
		"optionC": "computer",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "younger brother"
	},

	{
		"question": "第一",
		"pinyin": "dì yī",
		"optionA": "The first; number 1",
		"optionB": "sorry",
		"optionC": "computer",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "The first; number 1"
	},

	{
		"question": "懂",
		"pinyin": "dǒng",
		"optionA": "to read; to study",
		"optionB": "understand; know",
		"optionC": "computer",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "understand; know"
	},

	{
		"question": "对",
		"pinyin": "duì",
		"optionA": "to read; to study",
		"optionB": "sorry",
		"optionC": "correct; a pair; to face; be opposite; to; towards",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "correct; a pair; to face; be opposite; to; towards"
	},

	{
		"question": "房间",
		"pinyin": "fáng jiān",
		"optionA": "to read; to study",
		"optionB": "room",
		"optionC": "many; much; a lot of; more than",
		"optionD": "eat",
		"answer": "room"
	},

	{
		"question": "非常",
		"pinyin": "fēi cháng",
		"optionA": "to read; to study",
		"optionB": "how much; how many; which (number)",
		"optionC": "many; much; a lot of; more than",
		"optionD": "extraordinary; very；really;  strong emphasis",
		"answer": "extraordinary; very；really;  strong emphasis"
	},

	{
		"question": "服务员",
		"pinyin": "fú wù yuán",
		"optionA": "to read; to study",
		"optionB": "waiter/waitress; server; attendant",
		"optionC": "many; much; a lot of; more than",
		"optionD": "son",
		"answer": "waiter/waitress; server; attendant"
	},

	{
		"question": "高",
		"pinyin": "gāo",
		"optionA": "to read; to study",
		"optionB": "two (Kangxi radical 7)",
		"optionC": "high; tall (Kangxi radical 189)",
		"optionD": "son",
		"answer": "high; tall (Kangxi radical 189)"
	},

	{
		"question": "告诉",
		"pinyin": "gào su",
		"optionA": "to tell; inform",
		"optionB": "two (Kangxi radical 7)",
		"optionC": "restaurant; hotel",
		"optionD": "son",
		"answer": "to tell; inform"
	},

	{
		"question": "哥哥",
		"pinyin": "gē ge",
		"optionA": "aeroplane",
		"optionB": "two (Kangxi radical 7)",
		"optionC": "restaurant; hotel",
		"optionD": "older brother",
		"answer": "older brother"
	},

	{
		"question": "给",
		"pinyin": "gěi",
		"optionA": "aeroplane",
		"optionB": "to give; to grant; (passive particle)",
		"optionC": "restaurant; hotel",
		"optionD": "minute; (mw for time)",
		"answer": "to give; to grant; (passive particle)"
	},

	{
		"question": "公共汽车",
		"pinyin": "gōng gòng qì chē",
		"optionA": "(public) bus",
		"optionB": "happy; glad; willing (do something)",
		"optionC": "restaurant; hotel",
		"optionD": "minute; (mw for time)",
		"answer": "(public) bus"
	},

	{
		"question": "公司",
		"pinyin": "gōng sī",
		"optionA": "general measure word",
		"optionB": "happy; glad; willing (do something)",
		"optionC": "restaurant; hotel",
		"optionD": "company; corporation",
		"answer": "company; corporation"
	},

	{
		"question": "贵",
		"pinyin": "guì",
		"optionA": "general measure word",
		"optionB": "expensive; noble; honorable; Guizhou province (abbreviation)",
		"optionC": "restaurant; hotel",
		"optionD": "work; a job",
		"answer": "expensive; noble; honorable; Guizhou province (abbreviation)"
	},

	{
		"question": "过",
		"pinyin": "guò",
		"optionA": "general measure word",
		"optionB": "dog",
		"optionC": "to pass; to cross; go over; (indicates a past experience)",
		"optionD": "work; a job",
		"answer": "to pass; to cross; go over; (indicates a past experience)"
	},

	{
		"question": "还",
		"pinyin": "hái",
		"optionA": "general measure word",
		"optionB": "dog",
		"optionC": "Chinese language",
		"optionD": "still; yet; in addition; even",
		"answer": "still; yet; in addition; even"
	},

	{
		"question": "孩子",
		"pinyin": "hái zi",
		"optionA": "child; children; son or daughter",
		"optionB": "dog",
		"optionC": "Chinese language",
		"optionD": "good; well; nice; very; quite",
		"answer": "child; children; son or daughter"
	},

	{
		"question": "好吃",
		"pinyin": "hǎo chī",
		"optionA": "number; day of a month; (mw for ordinal numbers)",
		"optionB": "tasty",
		"optionC": "Chinese language",
		"optionD": "good; well; nice; very; quite",
		"answer": "tasty"
	},

	{
		"question": "黑",
		"pinyin": "hēi",
		"optionA": "and; with; harmony",
		"optionB": "black; dark (Kangxi radical 203); Heilongjiang province (abbreviation)",
		"optionC": "Chinese language",
		"optionD": "good; well; nice; very; quite",
		"answer": "black; dark (Kangxi radical 203); Heilongjiang province (abbreviation)"
	},

	{
		"question": "红",
		"pinyin": "hóng",
		"optionA": "and; with; harmony",
		"optionB": "to drink; interjection expressing surprise",
		"optionC": "red; symbol of success; bonus; popular",
		"optionD": "good; well; nice; very; quite",
		"answer": "red; symbol of success; bonus; popular"
	},

	{
		"question": "火车站",
		"pinyin": "huǒ chē zhàn",
		"optionA": "and; with; harmony",
		"optionB": "to drink; interjection expressing surprise",
		"optionC": "very; rather; quite; (adverb of degree)",
		"optionD": "train station",
		"answer": "train station"
	},

	{
		"question": "机场",
		"pinyin": "jī chǎng",
		"optionA": "and; with; harmony",
		"optionB": "airport; airfield",
		"optionC": "very; rather; quite; (adverb of degree)",
		"optionD": "rear; back; behind",
		"answer": "airport; airfield"
	},

	{
		"question": "鸡蛋",
		"pinyin": "jī dàn",
		"optionA": "(chicken) egg",
		"optionB": "to return; to reply; to go back; (mw for matters or actions)",
		"optionC": "very; rather; quite; (adverb of degree)",
		"optionD": "rear; back; behind",
		"answer": "(chicken) egg"
	},

	{
		"question": "件",
		"pinyin": "jiàn",
		"optionA": "know how; be good at; be likely to",
		"optionB": "(mw for things, clothes, and items)",
		"optionC": "very; rather; quite; (adverb of degree)",
		"optionD": "rear; back; behind",
		"answer": "(mw for things, clothes, and items)"
	},

	{
		"question": "教室",
		"pinyin": "jiào shì",
		"optionA": "know how; be good at; be likely to",
		"optionB": "how many; several; a few | almost (Kangxi radical 16)",
		"optionC": "very; rather; quite; (adverb of degree)",
		"optionD": "classroom",
		"answer": "classroom"
	},

	{
		"question": "姐姐",
		"pinyin": "jiě jie",
		"optionA": "know how; be good at; be likely to",
		"optionB": "to call; called; to yell",
		"optionC": "older sister",
		"optionD": "family; home; household",
		"answer": "older sister"
	},

	{
		"question": "介绍",
		"pinyin": "jiè shào",
		"optionA": "know how; be good at; be likely to",
		"optionB": "to call; called; to yell",
		"optionC": "to introduce; recommend; introduction",
		"optionD": "family; home; household",
		"answer": "to introduce; recommend; introduction"
	},

	{
		"question": "进",
		"pinyin": "jìn",
		"optionA": "nine",
		"optionB": "enter; come in",
		"optionC": "today; at the present; now",
		"optionD": "family; home; household",
		"answer": "enter; come in"
	},

	{
		"question": "近",
		"pinyin": "jìn",
		"optionA": "nine",
		"optionB": "to open; to start; to turn on; to operate (a vehicle)",
		"optionC": "near; close (to)",
		"optionD": "family; home; household",
		"answer": "near; close (to)"
	},

	{
		"question": "就",
		"pinyin": "jiù",
		"optionA": "nine",
		"optionB": "to open; to start; to turn on; to operate (a vehicle)",
		"optionC": "then; at once; just; only; with regard to",
		"optionD": "family; home; household",
		"answer": "then; at once; just; only; with regard to"
	},

	{
		"question": "觉得",
		"pinyin": "jué de",
		"optionA": "feel; think",
		"optionB": "to open; to start; to turn on; to operate (a vehicle)",
		"optionC": "see; catch sight of",
		"optionD": "family; home; household",
		"answer": "feel; think"
	},

	{
		"question": "咖啡",
		"pinyin": "kā fēi",
		"optionA": "lump; (mw: piece, chunk, sum of money)",
		"optionB": "coffee",
		"optionC": "see; catch sight of",
		"optionD": "come; arrive; ever since; next",
		"answer": "coffee"
	},

	{
		"question": "开始",
		"pinyin": "kāi shǐ",
		"optionA": "begin; to start; beginning",
		"optionB": "teacher",
		"optionC": "see; catch sight of",
		"optionD": "come; arrive; ever since; next",
		"answer": "begin; to start; beginning"
	},

	{
		"question": "考试",
		"pinyin": "kǎo shì",
		"optionA": "test; exam; to give or take a test",
		"optionB": "teacher",
		"optionC": "see; catch sight of",
		"optionD": "come; arrive; ever since; next",
		"answer": "test; exam; to give or take a test"
	},

	{
		"question": "可能",
		"pinyin": "kě néng",
		"optionA": "possible; maybe",
		"optionB": "teacher",
		"optionC": "cold",
		"optionD": "come; arrive; ever since; next",
		"answer": "possible; maybe"
	},

	{
		"question": "可以",
		"pinyin": "kě yǐ",
		"optionA": "can; may; possible; okay",
		"optionB": "teacher",
		"optionC": "cold",
		"optionD": "come; arrive; ever since; next",
		"answer": "can; may; possible; okay"
	},

	{
		"question": "课",
		"pinyin": "kè",
		"optionA": "class; subject; lesson; course",
		"optionB": "teacher",
		"optionC": "cold",
		"optionD": "six",
		"answer": "class; subject; lesson; course"
	},

	{
		"question": "快",
		"pinyin": "kuài",
		"optionA": "fast; quick; swift",
		"optionB": "teacher",
		"optionC": "cold",
		"optionD": "six",
		"answer": "fast; quick; swift"
	},

	{
		"question": "快乐",
		"pinyin": "kuài lè",
		"optionA": "mum; mama; mam; mother",
		"optionB": "teacher",
		"optionC": "happy",
		"optionD": "six",
		"answer": "happy"
	},

	{
		"question": "累",
		"pinyin": "lèi",
		"optionA": "mum; mama; mam; mother",
		"optionB": "tired",
		"optionC": "(question particle for yes/no questions)",
		"optionD": "six",
		"answer": "tired"
	},

	{
		"question": "离",
		"pinyin": "lí",
		"optionA": "mum; mama; mam; mother",
		"optionB": "to buy",
		"optionC": "leave; depart; go away; apart from",
		"optionD": "cat",
		"answer": "leave; depart; go away; apart from"
	},

	{
		"question": "两",
		"pinyin": "liǎng",
		"optionA": "two; 2; both; (unit of weight equal to 50 grams)",
		"optionB": "to buy",
		"optionC": "(question particle for yes/no questions)",
		"optionD": "cat",
		"answer": "two; 2; both; (unit of weight equal to 50 grams)"
	},

	{
		"question": "零",
		"pinyin": "líng",
		"optionA": "it doesn't matter; never mind",
		"optionB": "to buy",
		"optionC": "(question particle for yes/no questions)",
		"optionD": "zero; remnant",
		"answer": "zero; remnant"
	},

	{
		"question": "路",
		"pinyin": "lù",
		"optionA": "it doesn't matter; never mind",
		"optionB": "road; path; journey; route",
		"optionC": "(question particle for yes/no questions)",
		"optionD": "not have; there is not; haven't; hasn't",
		"answer": "road; path; journey; route"
	},

	{
		"question": "旅游",
		"pinyin": "lǚ yóu",
		"optionA": "trip; journey; tour",
		"optionB": "(cooked) rice",
		"optionC": "(question particle for yes/no questions)",
		"optionD": "not have; there is not; haven't; hasn't",
		"answer": "trip; journey; tour"
	},

	{
		"question": "卖",
		"pinyin": "mài",
		"optionA": "name",
		"optionB": "(cooked) rice",
		"optionC": "tomorrow",
		"optionD": "to sell",
		"answer": "to sell"
	},

	{
		"question": "慢",
		"pinyin": "màn",
		"optionA": "name",
		"optionB": "(cooked) rice",
		"optionC": "tomorrow",
		"optionD": "slow",
		"answer": "slow"
	},

	{
		"question": "忙",
		"pinyin": "máng",
		"optionA": "name",
		"optionB": "busy",
		"optionC": "tomorrow",
		"optionD": "which; how",
		"answer": "busy"
	},

	{
		"question": "每",
		"pinyin": "měi",
		"optionA": "each; every",
		"optionB": "where; wherever (Beijing accent)",
		"optionC": "tomorrow",
		"optionD": "which; how",
		"answer": "each; every"
	},

	{
		"question": "妹妹",
		"pinyin": "mèi mei",
		"optionA": "that; in that case; then",
		"optionB": "where; wherever (Beijing accent)",
		"optionC": "tomorrow",
		"optionD": "younger sister",
		"answer": "younger sister"
	},

	{
		"question": "门",
		"pinyin": "mén",
		"optionA": "that; in that case; then",
		"optionB": "where; wherever (Beijing accent)",
		"optionC": "tomorrow",
		"optionD": "door; opening; gate (Kangxi radical 169)",
		"answer": "door; opening; gate (Kangxi radical 169)"
	},

	{
		"question": "面条",
		"pinyin": "miàn tiáo",
		"optionA": "that; in that case; then",
		"optionB": "noodles",
		"optionC": "tomorrow",
		"optionD": "can; be able; capable; energy; ability",
		"answer": "noodles"
	},

	{
		"question": "男",
		"pinyin": "nán",
		"optionA": "that; in that case; then",
		"optionB": "you (singular)",
		"optionC": "male",
		"optionD": "can; be able; capable; energy; ability",
		"answer": "male"
	},

	{
		"question": "您",
		"pinyin": "nín",
		"optionA": "that; in that case; then",
		"optionB": "you (singular)",
		"optionC": "year",
		"optionD": "you (polite)",
		"answer": "you (polite)"
	},

	{
		"question": "牛奶",
		"pinyin": "niú nǎi",
		"optionA": "that; in that case; then",
		"optionB": "cow's milk",
		"optionC": "year",
		"optionD": "daughter",
		"answer": "cow's milk"
	},

	{
		"question": "女",
		"pinyin": "nǚ",
		"optionA": "woman; female (Kangxi radical 38)",
		"optionB": "friend",
		"optionC": "year",
		"optionD": "daughter",
		"answer": "woman; female (Kangxi radical 38)"
	},

	{
		"question": "旁边",
		"pinyin": "páng biān",
		"optionA": "pretty; beautiful",
		"optionB": "friend",
		"optionC": "beside, side",
		"optionD": "daughter",
		"answer": "beside, side"
	},

	{
		"question": "跑步",
		"pinyin": "pǎo bù",
		"optionA": "pretty; beautiful",
		"optionB": "friend",
		"optionC": "apple",
		"optionD": "to run; to jog",
		"answer": "to run; to jog"
	},

	{
		"question": "便宜",
		"pinyin": "pián yi",
		"optionA": "cheap",
		"optionB": "friend",
		"optionC": "apple",
		"optionD": "seven",
		"answer": "cheap"
	},

	{
		"question": "票",
		"pinyin": "piào",
		"optionA": "in front; fore; at the head",
		"optionB": "friend",
		"optionC": "ticket; bank note; a vote",
		"optionD": "seven",
		"answer": "ticket; bank note; a vote"
	},

	{
		"question": "妻子",
		"pinyin": "qī zi",
		"optionA": "in front; fore; at the head",
		"optionB": "wife",
		"optionC": "money; coin",
		"optionD": "seven",
		"answer": "wife"
	},

	{
		"question": "起床",
		"pinyin": "qǐ chuáng",
		"optionA": "in front; fore; at the head",
		"optionB": "please; invite; to request | treat",
		"optionC": "get out of bed",
		"optionD": "seven",
		"answer": "get out of bed"
	},

	{
		"question": "千",
		"pinyin": "qiān",
		"optionA": "one thousand",
		"optionB": "please; invite; to request | treat",
		"optionC": "go; to leave",
		"optionD": "seven",
		"answer": "one thousand"
	},

	{
		"question": "铅笔",
		"pinyin": "qiān bǐ",
		"optionA": "heat; hot; heat up",
		"optionB": "pencil",
		"optionC": "go; to leave",
		"optionD": "seven",
		"answer": "pencil"
	},

	{
		"question": "晴",
		"pinyin": "qíng",
		"optionA": "heat; hot; heat up",
		"optionB": "person; man; people (Kangxi radical 9)",
		"optionC": "go; to leave",
		"optionD": "clear; fine (as of weather)",
		"answer": "clear; fine (as of weather)"
	},

	{
		"question": "去年",
		"pinyin": "qù nián",
		"optionA": "last year",
		"optionB": "person; man; people (Kangxi radical 9)",
		"optionC": "go; to leave",
		"optionD": "know; recognize; acquainted with (a person)",
		"answer": "last year"
	},

	{
		"question": "让",
		"pinyin": "ràng",
		"optionA": "three",
		"optionB": "ask; let; yield",
		"optionC": "go; to leave",
		"optionD": "know; recognize; acquainted with (a person)",
		"answer": "ask; let; yield"
	},

	{
		"question": "日",
		"pinyin": "rì",
		"optionA": "three",
		"optionB": "shop，store",
		"optionC": "sun; day; date; time (Kangxi radical 72)",
		"optionD": "know; recognize; acquainted with (a person)",
		"answer": "sun; day; date; time (Kangxi radical 72)"
	},

	{
		"question": "上班",
		"pinyin": "shàng bān",
		"optionA": "three",
		"optionB": "shop，store",
		"optionC": "above; up; on top; get on; go up",
		"optionD": "go to work; be on duty",
		"answer": "go to work; be on duty"
	},

	{
		"question": "身体",
		"pinyin": "shēn tǐ",
		"optionA": "health; (human) body",
		"optionB": "shop，store",
		"optionC": "above; up; on top; get on; go up",
		"optionD": "late morning (before noon)",
		"answer": "health; (human) body"
	},

	{
		"question": "生病",
		"pinyin": "shēng bìng",
		"optionA": "few; little; lack; lose",
		"optionB": "get sick; fall ill",
		"optionC": "above; up; on top; get on; go up",
		"optionD": "late morning (before noon)",
		"answer": "get sick; fall ill"
	},

	{
		"question": "生日",
		"pinyin": "shēng rì",
		"optionA": "few; little; lack; lose",
		"optionB": "who",
		"optionC": "birthday",
		"optionD": "late morning (before noon)",
		"answer": "birthday"
	},

	{
		"question": "时间",
		"pinyin": "shí jiān",
		"optionA": "time; period",
		"optionB": "who",
		"optionC": "what; whatever; something",
		"optionD": "late morning (before noon)",
		"answer": "time; period"
	},

	{
		"question": "事情",
		"pinyin": "shì qíng",
		"optionA": "ten (Kangxi radical 24)",
		"optionB": "who",
		"optionC": "what; whatever; something",
		"optionD": "matter; affair; thing; business",
		"answer": "matter; affair; thing; business"
	},

	{
		"question": "手表",
		"pinyin": "shǒu biǎo",
		"optionA": "ten (Kangxi radical 24)",
		"optionB": "wristwatch",
		"optionC": "what; whatever; something",
		"optionD": "time; length of time; moment",
		"answer": "wristwatch"
	},

	{
		"question": "手机",
		"pinyin": "shǒu jī",
		"optionA": "mobile (cell) phone",
		"optionB": "be; is; are; am",
		"optionC": "what; whatever; something",
		"optionD": "time; length of time; moment",
		"answer": "mobile (cell) phone"
	},

	{
		"question": "说话",
		"pinyin": "shuō huà",
		"optionA": "book; letter",
		"optionB": "be; is; are; am",
		"optionC": "to talk; speak",
		"optionD": "time; length of time; moment",
		"answer": "to talk; speak"
	},

	{
		"question": "送",
		"pinyin": "sòng",
		"optionA": "book; letter",
		"optionB": "be; is; are; am",
		"optionC": "water (Kangxi radical 85)",
		"optionD": "deliver; to carry; to give; send",
		"answer": "deliver; to carry; to give; send"
	},

	{
		"question": "虽然",
		"pinyin": "suī rán",
		"optionA": "book; letter",
		"optionB": "be; is; are; am",
		"optionC": "although; even though",
		"optionD": "fruit",
		"answer": "although; even though"
	},

	{
		"question": "但是",
		"pinyin": "dàn shì",
		"optionA": "book; letter",
		"optionB": "but; however",
		"optionC": "to sleep; go to bed",
		"optionD": "fruit",
		"answer": "but; however"
	},

	{
		"question": "它",
		"pinyin": "tā",
		"optionA": "it",
		"optionB": "speak; to say; to talk",
		"optionC": "to sleep; go to bed",
		"optionD": "fruit",
		"answer": "it"
	},

	{
		"question": "踢足球",
		"pinyin": "tī zú qiú",
		"optionA": "four",
		"optionB": "speak; to say; to talk",
		"optionC": "to sleep; go to bed",
		"optionD": "to play football/soccer",
		"answer": "to play football/soccer"
	},

	{
		"question": "题",
		"pinyin": "tí",
		"optionA": "four",
		"optionB": "speak; to say; to talk",
		"optionC": "topic; subject; question on a test or assignment",
		"optionD": "years old",
		"answer": "topic; subject; question on a test or assignment"
	},

	{
		"question": "跳舞",
		"pinyin": "tiào wǔ",
		"optionA": "four",
		"optionB": "to dance",
		"optionC": "he; him",
		"optionD": "years old",
		"answer": "to dance"
	},

	{
		"question": "外",
		"pinyin": "wài",
		"optionA": "outer; outside; in addition; foreign",
		"optionB": "she; her",
		"optionC": "he; him",
		"optionD": "years old",
		"answer": "outer; outside; in addition; foreign"
	},

	{
		"question": "完",
		"pinyin": "wán",
		"optionA": "too (much); excessively; highest; greatest",
		"optionB": "she; her",
		"optionC": "he; him",
		"optionD": "to finish; be over; complete",
		"answer": "to finish; be over; complete"
	},

	{
		"question": "玩",
		"pinyin": "wán",
		"optionA": "too (much); excessively; highest; greatest",
		"optionB": "she; her",
		"optionC": "to play; have a good time; visit; enjoy",
		"optionD": "weather",
		"answer": "to play; have a good time; visit; enjoy"
	},

	{
		"question": "晚上",
		"pinyin": "wǎn shang",
		"optionA": "evening; night",
		"optionB": "fellow student; schoolmate",
		"optionC": "listen; hear; heed",
		"optionD": "weather",
		"answer": "evening; night"
	},

	{
		"question": "往",
		"pinyin": "wǎng",
		"optionA": "too (much); excessively; highest; greatest",
		"optionB": "fellow student; schoolmate",
		"optionC": "listen; hear; heed",
		"optionD": "to go (in a direction); towards; in the past",
		"answer": "to go (in a direction); towards; in the past"
	},

	{
		"question": "为什么",
		"pinyin": "wèi shén me",
		"optionA": "why?; for what reason?",
		"optionB": "fellow student; schoolmate",
		"optionC": "listen; hear; heed",
		"optionD": "hey; hello (on the phone)",
		"answer": "why?; for what reason?"
	},

	{
		"question": "问",
		"pinyin": "wèn",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "fellow student; schoolmate",
		"optionC": "ask; inquire",
		"optionD": "hey; hello (on the phone)",
		"answer": "ask; inquire"
	},

	{
		"question": "问题",
		"pinyin": "wèn tí",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "question; problem",
		"optionC": "we; us",
		"optionD": "hey; hello (on the phone)",
		"answer": "question; problem"
	},

	{
		"question": "西瓜",
		"pinyin": "xī guā",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "five",
		"optionC": "we; us",
		"optionD": "watermelon",
		"answer": "watermelon"
	},

	{
		"question": "希望",
		"pinyin": "xī wàng",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "five",
		"optionC": "to hope; wish for; to desire",
		"optionD": "to like; be fond of",
		"answer": "to hope; wish for; to desire"
	},

	{
		"question": "洗",
		"pinyin": "xǐ",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "to wash; bathe",
		"optionC": "descend; fall; below; down; next; the second (of two parts)",
		"optionD": "to like; be fond of",
		"answer": "to wash; bathe"
	},

	{
		"question": "小时",
		"pinyin": "xiǎo shí",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "afternoon",
		"optionC": "hour",
		"optionD": "to like; be fond of",
		"answer": "hour"
	},

	{
		"question": "笑",
		"pinyin": "xiào",
		"optionA": "I; me",
		"optionB": "afternoon",
		"optionC": "to rain",
		"optionD": "to laugh; to smile",
		"answer": "to laugh; to smile"
	},

	{
		"question": "新",
		"pinyin": "xīn",
		"optionA": "new; Xinjiang autonomous region (abbreviation)",
		"optionB": "afternoon",
		"optionC": "to rain",
		"optionD": "Mr.; Sir",
		"answer": "new; Xinjiang autonomous region (abbreviation)"
	},

	{
		"question": "姓",
		"pinyin": "xìng",
		"optionA": "now",
		"optionB": "surname; family name",
		"optionC": "to rain",
		"optionD": "Mr.; Sir",
		"answer": "surname; family name"
	},

	{
		"question": "休息",
		"pinyin": "xiū xi",
		"optionA": "now",
		"optionB": "think; believe; suppose; would like to; remember with longing; to miss",
		"optionC": "to rain",
		"optionD": "to rest; take a break",
		"answer": "to rest; take a break"
	},

	{
		"question": "雪",
		"pinyin": "xuě",
		"optionA": "now",
		"optionB": "snow",
		"optionC": "to rain",
		"optionD": "small; young (Kangxi radical 42)",
		"answer": "snow"
	},

	{
		"question": "颜色",
		"pinyin": "yán sè",
		"optionA": "color",
		"optionB": "young lady; miss; Ms.",
		"optionC": "to rain",
		"optionD": "small; young (Kangxi radical 42)",
		"answer": "color"
	},

	{
		"question": "眼睛",
		"pinyin": "yǎn jing",
		"optionA": "eye",
		"optionB": "young lady; miss; Ms.",
		"optionC": "to write; to compose",
		"optionD": "small; young (Kangxi radical 42)",
		"answer": "eye"
	},

	{
		"question": "羊肉",
		"pinyin": "yáng ròu",
		"optionA": "mutton; lamb",
		"optionB": "young lady; miss; Ms.",
		"optionC": "to write; to compose",
		"optionD": "small; young (Kangxi radical 42)",
		"answer": "mutton; lamb"
	},

	{
		"question": "药",
		"pinyin": "yào",
		"optionA": "to thank; thank you",
		"optionB": "young lady; miss; Ms.",
		"optionC": "to write; to compose",
		"optionD": "medicine; drug; cure; chemical",
		"answer": "medicine; drug; cure; chemical"
	},

	{
		"question": "要",
		"pinyin": "yào",
		"optionA": "to want; to need; will/shall; important",
		"optionB": "young lady; miss; Ms.",
		"optionC": "to write; to compose",
		"optionD": "week",
		"answer": "to want; to need; will/shall; important"
	},

	{
		"question": "也",
		"pinyin": "yě",
		"optionA": "student",
		"optionB": "also; too",
		"optionC": "to write; to compose",
		"optionD": "week",
		"answer": "also; too"
	},

	{
		"question": "一起",
		"pinyin": "yī qǐ",
		"optionA": "student",
		"optionB": "learn; to study; emulate",
		"optionC": "to write; to compose",
		"optionD": "together; in the same place",
		"answer": "together; in the same place"
	},

	{
		"question": "一下",
		"pinyin": "yī xià",
		"optionA": "student",
		"optionB": "learn; to study; emulate",
		"optionC": "a little bit/while; one time; once",
		"optionD": "school",
		"answer": "a little bit/while; one time; once"
	},

	{
		"question": "已经",
		"pinyin": "yǐ jīng",
		"optionA": "already",
		"optionB": "learn; to study; emulate",
		"optionC": "one; once; a (article) (Kangxi radical 1)",
		"optionD": "school",
		"answer": "already"
	},

	{
		"question": "意思",
		"pinyin": "yì si",
		"optionA": "a bit; a few; a little; Beijing accent",
		"optionB": "learn; to study; emulate",
		"optionC": "meaning; idea; opinion",
		"optionD": "school",
		"answer": "meaning; idea; opinion"
	},

	{
		"question": "因为",
		"pinyin": "yīn wèi",
		"optionA": "because",
		"optionB": "learn; to study; emulate",
		"optionC": "clothes",
		"optionD": "school",
		"answer": "because"
	},

	{
		"question": "所以",
		"pinyin": "suǒ yǐ",
		"optionA": "doctor",
		"optionB": "learn; to study; emulate",
		"optionC": "clothes",
		"optionD": "so; therefore; as a result",
		"answer": "so; therefore; as a result"
	},

	{
		"question": "阴",
		"pinyin": "yīn",
		"optionA": "doctor",
		"optionB": "cloudy (weather); yin (the negative principle of Yin and Yang); secret; the moon; negative; shade",
		"optionC": "clothes",
		"optionD": "hospital",
		"answer": "cloudy (weather); yin (the negative principle of Yin and Yang); secret; the moon; negative; shade"
	},

	{
		"question": "游泳",
		"pinyin": "yóu yǒng",
		"optionA": "doctor",
		"optionB": "chair",
		"optionC": "to swim",
		"optionD": "hospital",
		"answer": "to swim"
	},

	{
		"question": "右边",
		"pinyin": "yòu bian",
		"optionA": "the right (as opposed to left) side",
		"optionB": "chair",
		"optionC": "have; there is",
		"optionD": "hospital",
		"answer": "the right (as opposed to left) side"
	},

	{
		"question": "鱼",
		"pinyin": "yú",
		"optionA": "moon; month (Kangxi radical 74: moon | (Kangxi radical 130: flesh)",
		"optionB": "chair",
		"optionC": "have; there is",
		"optionD": "fish (Kangxi radical 195)",
		"answer": "fish (Kangxi radical 195)"
	},

	{
		"question": "远",
		"pinyin": "yuǎn",
		"optionA": "far; distant; remote",
		"optionB": "chair",
		"optionC": "have; there is",
		"optionD": "goodbye; see you later",
		"answer": "far; distant; remote"
	},

	{
		"question": "运动",
		"pinyin": "yùn dòng",
		"optionA": "at; on; in; exist; (indicating an action in progress)",
		"optionB": "(physical) exercise; movement; sports; campaign",
		"optionC": "have; there is",
		"optionD": "goodbye; see you later",
		"answer": "(physical) exercise; movement; sports; campaign"
	},

	{
		"question": "再",
		"pinyin": "zài",
		"optionA": "again; once more",
		"optionB": "how",
		"optionC": "have; there is",
		"optionD": "goodbye; see you later",
		"answer": "again; once more"
	},

	{
		"question": "早上",
		"pinyin": "zǎo shang",
		"optionA": "how about; how is/was it",
		"optionB": "how",
		"optionC": "have; there is",
		"optionD": "(early) morning",
		"answer": "(early) morning"
	},

	{
		"question": "丈夫",
		"pinyin": "zhàng fu",
		"optionA": "how about; how is/was it",
		"optionB": "how",
		"optionC": "husband; man",
		"optionD": "this; these",
		"answer": "husband; man"
	},

	{
		"question": "找",
		"pinyin": "zhǎo",
		"optionA": "how about; how is/was it",
		"optionB": "try to find; look for; seek; to give change",
		"optionC": "China",
		"optionD": "this; these",
		"answer": "try to find; look for; seek; to give change"
	},

	{
		"question": "着",
		"pinyin": "zhe",
		"optionA": "how about; how is/was it",
		"optionB": "noon; midday",
		"optionC": "China",
		"optionD": "-ing (indicating action in progress)",
		"answer": "-ing (indicating action in progress)"
	},

	{
		"question": "真",
		"pinyin": "zhēn",
		"optionA": "how about; how is/was it",
		"optionB": "noon; midday",
		"optionC": "real; true; genuine",
		"optionD": "to live; reside; to stop",
		"answer": "real; true; genuine"
	},

	{
		"question": "正在",
		"pinyin": "zhèng zài",
		"optionA": "in the process of (doing something); currently",
		"optionB": "noon; midday",
		"optionC": "table; desk",
		"optionD": "to live; reside; to stop",
		"answer": "in the process of (doing something); currently"
	},

	{
		"question": "知道",
		"pinyin": "zhī dào",
		"optionA": "word; letter; character",
		"optionB": "to know; to be aware of",
		"optionC": "table; desk",
		"optionD": "to live; reside; to stop",
		"answer": "to know; to be aware of"
	},

	{
		"question": "准备",
		"pinyin": "zhǔn bèi",
		"optionA": "word; letter; character",
		"optionB": "yesterday",
		"optionC": "prepare; get ready",
		"optionD": "to live; reside; to stop",
		"answer": "prepare; get ready"
	},

	{
		"question": "走",
		"pinyin": "zuò",
		"optionA": "to walk; to go; to move (Kangxi radical 156)",
		"optionB": "yesterday",
		"optionC": "sit; take a seat",
		"optionD": "to live; reside; to stop",
		"answer": "to walk; to go; to move (Kangxi radical 156)"
	},

	{
		"question": "最",
		"pinyin": "zuì",
		"optionA": "word; letter; character",
		"optionB": "yesterday",
		"optionC": "the most; -est; (indicator for superlative)",
		"optionD": "to live; reside; to stop",
		"answer": "the most; -est; (indicator for superlative)"
	},

	{
		"question": "左边",
		"pinyin": "zuǒ bian",
		"optionA": "word; letter; character",
		"optionB": "the left side; the left",
		"optionC": "table; desk",
		"optionD": "to live; reside; to stop",
		"answer": "the left side; the left"
	}
]
